What year was she born?
How should I know?
You don't know?
Then how can you prove she's your boss's runaway concubine,
and not that you're out here in broad daylight
kidnapping a decent woman?
Kidnapping an innocent girl?
I misspoke earlier!
She's just a filthy whore from Minchun Pavilion!
I'm taking her back to Minchun Pavilion right now!
Everyone, don't listen to his nonsense!
She has a Good Citizen Pass!
What are you standing around for?
Get the hell out of here!
You just wait!
You, you, go guard the boat!
Yes, sir! The rest of you, lock down the pier!
Nobody leaves!
Move along! Break it up! Clear out!
Make a more convincing one next time.
Thank you.
With wolves ahead and tigers behind,
as of now,
you have nowhere to go.
How about this?
Come to the Sanshan Gang.
I'll get a doctor to treat your wounds.
Lay low for a few days.
You can leave once the heat dies down.
You...
Why are you helping me?
That commemorative badge you're wearing...
I have one too.
Dali, take her back.
Come with me.
Who's there at this hour?
What do you want?
I... I'm looking for Chen Dieyi.
What do you want with her?
I need her help.
Where are you from?
Min... Minchun Pavilion.
Get lost. She isn't here.
Please!
Just let me see her.
Just for a minute!
What's going on out there?
Nothing. Just a beggar.
Chen Dieyi! Chen Dieyi!
Please help me!
Open the door.
Sister Dieyi, she's from Minchun Pavilion.
The police were just here to investigate today.
She's big trouble.
Open the door.
Chen Dieyi! Chen Dieyi!
Please, save me!
Scissors, keys, knockout drug.
Everything you asked for is right here.
Whatever you do, don't say I gave them to you.
Here's the agreed payment.
Sister Yumei is dead.
Sister Furong is dead, too.
We really had no other choice
but to come to you.
Sister Yumei said you could help us.
Please, I beg you! Please!
Please help us!
I beg you!
Sister Dieyi, she's nothing but trouble.
She could drag the dance hall down with her.
We worked so hard to get where we are.
There's no need to risk it for her—
No, please! Don't!
Did that bitch run that way?
Search thoroughly!
Catch her and skin her alive!
Check everywhere!
Please...
Hide in here.
Boss Chen.
Why is it so noisy out there?
It's so late.
What's going on?
We're looking for a girl.
She ran this way.
Did you see her?
A girl?
She was running fast.
Looked like she went that way.
Thank you, Boss Chen. Thank you!
Let's go.
She escaped into Club Jasmine.
Club Jasmine caters to high officials and elites.
We didn't dare barge in to seize her.
Besides, Boss Chen, Hall Master Lian,
and Deputy Chief Li are childhood friends.
We can't afford to cross them.
Chen Dieyi is a pragmatic woman.
She won't ask for trouble.
Keep a tight watch on Club Jasmine.
Don't take your eyes off it!
Yes, sir. Right away.
What on earth happened?
Boss Chen...
Get up first.
Tell me what happened.
Here's what happened.
Over a month ago...
Besides, the four of us have no one else to turn to.
If we didn't come to you, we'd be as good as dead.
This is way too big.
Club Jasmine can't protect you.
You have to get out of here.
The Chairman was right after all.
Boss Chen is a smart one.
She wouldn't muddy the waters for some cheap whore.
After her!
Get her!
Stop, you bitch!
Stop right there!
Hurry!
Go!
Stop right there!
I just stepped outside,
why are you chasing me
like you've seen a ghost?
We've been tricked!
It's a diversion!
Go, go!
What are you doing here?
Dieyi asked me to come.
I thought I was the only one.
I finally managed to get rid of Wang Dali,
so why are you here playing third wheel?
And there's fresh Thousand-Layer Steamed Cake.
Here.
Haven't had this in ages. Have a seat.
Why didn't we meet at Club Jasmine?
My place is being watched.
It's not safe to meet you there.
Why?
The Rongcheng Coastal Defense Map was stolen.
As for the details,
I'll let the person involved explain everything.
Come on out.
Don't be afraid. They're all my friends.
Just tell us what you know.
That night...
Sun Hanji had us entertain VIP guests,
drug their drinks,
and steal the Rongcheng Coastal Defense Map.
Honored guests,
enjoy the music and drink your fill!
Great!
Take good care of them! Take good care!
All right.
Wake up. Wake up.
Sir.
At first, we didn't know what it was.
When we opened it, it was the Rongcheng Coastal Defense Map.
Sister Yumei said
that if we gave the defense map to Sun Hanji,
he would surely sell it to the Japanese.
Then Rongcheng would be doomed,
and we'd be condemned forever.
To avoid getting caught,
Sister Furong, who had studied painting,
made an exact copy of it.
Then she put the original back into the guest's briefcase,
completely undetected.
We may be courtesans,
but Chinese blood runs in our veins.
We could never do anything to harm our own people.
But if we didn't hand over the defense map,
Sun Hanji would never let us live.
Sister Yumei came up with a plan.
She divided the map into six pieces.
One piece for each of us.
While the guards at Minchun Pavilion weren't looking,
we escaped from Minchun Pavilion.
If we got caught,
we'd at least have a lifeline.
Sister Yumei had a patch of skin flayed off her,
because she had carved the map onto her back.
Sister Furong,
unable to bear the brutal torture,
handed over her piece and was killed anyway.
Now Qiushuang and Haitang
have been taken to Sun Hanji's manor,
their fates unknown.
Peony has gone missing, too.
Do you know Jin Xiaohua?
Peony's real name is Jin Xiaohua.
She's recovering at the Sanshan Gang now.
Don't worry.
Why does each of you
have a Club Jasmine commemorative badge?
During Club Jasmine's second anniversary,
we snuck out of Minchun Pavilion pretending to buy clothes.
Welcome, everyone! Thank you for coming!
Great! Wonderful!
Give me one! Give me one!
Here, there's one for everyone. Thank you!
Don't push! One at a time!
Everyone gets one! Give me one!
Give me one, please!
Thank you. Thank you.
Here you go.
Seeing the badge reminds us of Chen Dieyi,
and gives us hope that we can survive anything.
Then...
why...
No need to dwell on what doesn't matter.
Go on inside first.
We need to talk this over.
The situation is clear now.
The coastal defense map
must never fall into Sun Hanji's hands.
Otherwise, Rongcheng will be in grave peril.
Before the garrison notices,
the theft of the coastal defense map
must be dealt with quietly.
Once the Confidential Bureau finds out,
they, and all of us who know,
will all end up dead.
In short,
we must secure the map,
and protect them too.